<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<opportunities>
	<opportunity title="Turner Construction Internship" posted="3 Mar 31" logo="images/turner.jpg">
		<description ><![CDATA[
		In today’s competitive professional world, the most qualified job candidates have more than classroom experience. They leave college and enter the workforce with hands-on exposure in their chosen fields.
Turner places high value on scholarship and internship experience when making hiring decisions. Through our own internship program, we are shaping the future leaders of our company. 
Seniors! If you are interested in Architecture, engineering or construction management don’t miss this opportunity.

		<br/><br/>
		Application Deadline: April 24, 2015
		]]></description>
		<website>
		http://tinyurl.com/oznxbt5
		</website>
		<link></link>
	</opportunity>
	
		
	<opportunity title="Engineering Awareness Program" posted="3 Mar 31" logo="images/awares.jpg">
		<description ><![CDATA[
		Manhattan College's Engineering Awareness Program aims to introduce high 

school students to potential careers in the various fields of engineering.

At no cost to the students, the 10-day program focuses on science, engineering 

and SAT preparation and is co-sponsored by the ACE Mentorship Program, the 

Metropolitan Section of the American Society of Civil Engineers (ASCE) and the 

General Contractors' Association, as well as individual corporate sponsors. 

Rising juniors and seniors have the opportunity to become more exposed to the 

engineering field through guest speakers, experiments in mechanical (aerospace 

and energy), civil, electrical, environmental (water filtration) and computer 

engineering, class lectures and the college admission process.
<br><br>
<ol>
<li>This is a ten-day program which includes all of the following dates and times:</li>
<li>July  7th through 10th   from   8:30 AM to 3 PM</li>
<li>July  13th through 16th from   8:30 AM to 3 PM</li>
<li>July  20th and 21st        from  8:30 AM to 3 PM</li>
</ol>

		<br/>
		Application Deadline: April 24, 2015
		]]></description>
		<website>
		https://manhattan.edu/academics/engineering/high-school-engineering-awareness-program
		</website>
	</opportunity>
	
		<opportunity title="STEM Enrichment opportunities " posted="3 Mar 31" logo="images/stem.jpg">
		<description ><![CDATA[<br>
		Links to various summer and during the school opportunities involving Science, Technology, Engineering and Mathematics
<br><br>
		<ul>
<li>Rockefeller University Summer Science Research Program</li>
<li>Hofstra University Science Summer Research Program</li>
<li>Women in STEM High School (WISH)</li>
<li>Museum Education and Employment Program at the American Museum of Natural History</li>
<li>New York City Science and Engineering Fair (NYSEF)</li>
</ul>
		
		
		]]></description>
		<website>
		 http://www.rockefeller.edu/outreach/links
		</website>
	</opportunity>
	
	<opportunity title="STEM Institute" posted="3 Mar 31" logo="images/citycollege.jpg">
		<description ><![CDATA[
		The STEM Institute is a challenging academic enrichment program designed to encourage minority students in grade 9-11 to maximize their academic potential by providing them with an educational program in college-level study. The STEM Institute offers courses in the physical sciences, mathematics, English, engineering and computer programming.
<br>June 29 to August 7, 2015 Monday to Thursday 9:00 am – 4:00 pm

		<br/>
		<br>
	Application Deadline: April 24, 2015
		]]></description>
		<website>
		 http://stem.ccny.cuny.edu/
		</website>
	</opportunity>
</opportunities>
